var questions = [
    {
        question: "1.Waht does HTML stand for",
        answers: {
            a: "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language",
            b: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            c: "Home Tool Markup Language"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "2.Choose the correct HTML element to define important text",
        answers: {
            a: "<b>",
            b: "<strong>",
            c: "<important>"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "3.How can you make a numbered list?",
        answers: {
            a: "<ol>",
            b: "<list>",
            c: "<ul>"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "4.What does CSS stand for?",
        answers: {
            a: "Cascading Style Sheets",
            b: "Computer Style Sheets",
            c: "Colorful Style Sheets"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "5.Which property is used to change the background color?",
        answers: {
            a: "color",
            b: "bgcolor",
            c: "background-color"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "6.Which CSS property controls the text size?",
        answer: {
            a: "text-size",
            b: "text-style",
            c: "font-size"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "7.How do you select elements with class name 'test'?",
        answer: {
            a: "#test",
            b: ".test",
            c: "*test"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "8.Where is the correct place to insert a JavaScript?",
        answer: {
            a: "Both the <head> section and the <body> section are correct",
            b: "The <head> section",
            c: "The <body> section"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: '9.How do you write "Hello World" in an alert box?',
        answer: {
            a: 'alertBox("Hello World");',
            b: 'alert("Hello Wrold")',
            c: 'msg("Hello World")'
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "10.What is the correct way to write a JavaScript array?",
        answer: {
            a: 'var colors = ["red", "green", "blue"]',
            b: 'var colors = (1:"red", 2:"green", 3:"blue")',
            c: 'var colors = "red", "green", "blue"'
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    }
]




// function generateQuiz(questions, quizContainer, resultsContainer, submitButton){

// 	function showQuestions(questions, quizContainer){
// 		// code will go here
// 	}

// 	function showResults(questions, quizContainer, resultsContainer){
// 		// code will go here
// 	}

// 	// show the questions
// 	showQuestions(questions, quizContainer);

// 	// when user clicks submit, show results
// 	submitButton.onclick = function(){
// 		showResults(questions, quizContainer, resultsContainer);
// 	}
// }


// var myQuestions = [
// 	{
// 		question: "What is 10/2?",
// 		answers: {
// 			a: '3',
// 			b: '5',
// 			c: '115'
// 		},
// 		correctAnswer: 'b'
// 	},
// 	{
// 		question: "What is 30/3?",
// 		answers: {
// 			a: '3',
// 			b: '5',
// 			c: '10'
// 		},
// 		correctAnswer: 'c'
// 	}
// ];